promotioncode.org 2016-12-04

# Privacy Policy of PromotionCode.org

PromotionCode.org is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our site's visitors. You can visit our website and browse the pages on our site without disclosing your name, e-mail address, log-in, password or any other type of personally identifiable information.

If you elect, as so many of you do, to participate in our mailing list created to alert you to new promotion codes for any or all of our retailers, you will give us, and we will store, your email address only. According to the parameters you set, you will be alerted from time to time of new discounts by email. You may opt out of this service at any time by responding to the directions to opt out at the bottom of the email you receive. We do not send regularly scheduled e-mails, such as monthly emails. We only contact you if we have something important to say.

If you choose to provide us with your email address we will not rent, share, or sell your e-mail address to any third party under any circumstances.

Cookies: A cookie is a tiny data file that contains a unique identification number that is transferred from any web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site can identify unique visitors to the site and track users' activities on the web site. PromotionCode.org uses cookies but their use does not tell us any personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address or email address.

Links on PromotionCode.org: Since the nature of PromotionCode.org is to provide discount information for use on other web sites, we provide links to hundreds of retailer web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites and encourage you to review the privacy policies of those sites before given them your personal information.

Security: PromotionCode.org keeps technical, electronic, physical and other safeguards in place to protect both our system and any personal information we may hold. If you would like to contact our Privacy Officer, you can initiate contact [here](http://www.promotioncode.org/contactus.php). Please set forth the nature of your request or concern and provide the Privacy Officer with a way to contact you.

Updates to Privacy Policy: From time to time, PromotionCode.org reviews its privacy policies and procedures to ensure they remain current.
